[{"id": 1975, "question": "We found out that Jenny was suffering hearing loss when she was four and a half years old. Several operations and speech classes later, when she was seven, we found out that Jenny had Juvenile Rheumatoid Arthritis . She could not put pressure on the heels of her feet, so she walked on tiptoe , and when the pain became unbearable, I carried her. Jenny was fortunate, though, because she did not suffer the deformities , often associated with JRA. All through grade school, and on into high school, Jenny suffered, yet never complained. She took her medicine, and I would often wrap her feet in steaming towels, and hold her until the pain eased. But, as soon as she could stand the pain, Jenny, immediately, carried on, as though she were pain-free. She wore a smile on her face, a song on her lips,...\n\nQ: In Jack's opinion, what was the main reason why the School Football Team won?", "options": ["The coach's proper instruction.", "Teammate's cooperation.", "Jenny's inspiring action.", "The team's good luck."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 10, "question": "Give it five minutes I used to be a hothead. Whenever anyone said anything, I'd think of a way to disagree. I'd push back hard if something didn't fit my world-view. It's like I had to be first with an opinion -- as if being first meant something. But what it really meant was that I wasn't thinking hard enough about the problem. The faster you react, the less you think. Not always, but often. This came to a head back in 2007. I was speaking at the Business Innovation Factory conference in Providence, RI. So was Richard Saul Wurman. After my talk Richard came up to introduce himself and compliment my talk. That was very generous of him. He certainly didn't have to do that. And what did I do? I pushed back at him about the talk he gave. While he was making his points on stage, I was taking a...\n\nQ: What did the author do while Richard was talking in the business conference?", "options": ["He kept notes for things that he did not agree with.", "He pushed Richard and beat him.", "He was preparing for his own speech.", "He was getting ready to compliment him."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1673, "question": "In 1905, as part of his Special Theory of Relativity, Albert Einstein published the point that a large amount of energy could be released from a small amount of matter. This was expressed by the equation E = mc2. But bombs were not what Einstein had in mind when he published this equation. In 1929, he publicly declared that if a war broke out he would \"refuse to do war service, direct or indirect....\" His position would change in 1933, as the result of Adolf Hitler's coming into power in Germany. Einstein's greatest role in the invention of the atomic bomb was signing a letter to President Franklin Roosevelt urging that the bomb be built because some physicists feared that Germany might be working on an atomic bomb. Among those concerned were physicists Leo Szilard and Eugene Wigner. But t...\n\nQ: The best title for the passage would be   _  .", "options": ["A Story of Albert Einstein", "Albert Einstein and the Atomic Bomb", "It was Unfair for Einstein", "How the Atomic Bomb was Invented"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1716, "question": "Healthy relationships are fun and make you feel good about yourself. The relationships that you make in your teenage years will be a special pan of your life. They will teach you some of the most important lessons about who you are. This may help you understand different kinds of relationships, what makes each relationship special, and how to communicate in a positive way. What makes a relationship healthy? Communication and Sharing: The most important part of any healthy relationship between two people is being able to talk and listen to each other. You and the other person can find out what your common interests are. You can share your feelings with the other person and trust that he or she will be there to listen to you and support you. In healthy relationships, people don't lie. Commun...\n\nQ: Which of the following relationships is healthy?", "options": ["You feel upset when you are around someone.", "You like to talk to someone and listen to him or her.", "Giving without taking.", "You feel that you have to spend time with him or her."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1107, "question": "\"Family\" is of course an _ word. But when British people say that their society is based on family life, they are thinking of \"family\" in its narrow, peculiarly European sense of mother ,father and children living together alone in their own house as an economic and social unit. Thus, every British marriage indicates the beginning of a new and independent family--hence the tremendous importance of marriage in British life. For both the man and the woman, marriage means leaving one's parents and starting one's own life. The man's first duty will then be to his wife, and the wife's to her husband. He will be entirely responsible for her financial support, and she for the running of the new home. Their children will be their common responsibility and theirs alone. Neither the wife's parents n...\n\nQ: With regard to marriage in Britain, present day girls differ from former time girls in   _  .", "options": ["the right marry", "more parental support", "choosing husbands", "social position"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2196, "question": "Medicine comes in lots of different packages. Painkillers in a tablet can make your headache go away. Antibiotic cream from a tube can prevent your cuts from becoming infected. But can medicine come packaged in chicken eggs? A team of scientists from Scotland say \"yes\". They've engineered special chickens that lay eggs with disease-treating drugs inside. These eggs come from chickens that have been engineered to produce certain drugs inside their egg whites. These drugs are made of molecules called proteins . Animals make thousands of proteins -- they're the main element in skin, hair, milk and meat. Since animals can make proteins easily, they're good candidates for making protein drugs. Researchers have already made cows, sheep and goats produce protein drugs in their milk. But chickens ...\n\nQ: If you cut your finger, you may use   _   to cure it.", "options": ["painkillers in a tablet", "antibiotic cream from a tube", "chicken eggs", "protein drugs"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2377, "question": "Tim Welford, aged 33, and Dom Mee, aged 30, both from England, were keen on (=\"like...\" very much) rowing boats. They made a plan to row across the Pacific Ocean from Japan to San Francisco. The name of their rowboat was \"Crackers\". It was about seven meters long. They set out from Japan on May 17,2001. They had rowed nearly 5,500 miles when their boat was hit by a fishing ship on September 17,2001. Luckily they both escaped unharmed, but their boat was badly damaged and they had to abandon( =\" stop)their\" journey. In a radio interview, Dom expressed his disappointment and explained how the accident took place. \"A fishing ship came towards us with nobody on the bridge and ran us down. It all happened so quickly. I managed to dive into the water. Tim felt it would be safer to stay on board....\n\nQ: 42. According to Dom, the main reason for the accident was that   _   .", "options": ["Tim and Dom were too careless", "the speed of the fishing ship was too fast", "nobody on the fishing ship saw them", "their rowboat was not strong enough"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 208, "question": "College is a fresh start, and a chance to make new friends. These friends may become your lifelong friends, or the person you want to spend the rest of your life with. Whether you are going to a nearby college or the university far away from home, you are likely to meet new people wherever you are. Here are some advice to help you make friends at college. Clearly, your classmates are all possible friends! Get to class early on the first day, and if you get there early enough, you will be in the room, or waiting outside it, with one other person, or a small group. A good casual opener would be to ask if you're in the right classroom, then introduce yourself, and explain that you're new, and a _ . Do this at all of your classes, and you will have a group of friends that you can make study gr...\n\nQ: Which piece of advice is NOT given by the author?", "options": ["Make friends with your classmates.", "Take part in dorm activities.", "Do the same team sports as your classmates.", "Join as many organizations as possible."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1620, "question": "Your children's teacher will be providing extra time for test preparation. This school year's test will be held on January 8 and 9. The test preparation time is open to all students, and we strongly encourage your children to attend. This year we are changing the time for our test preparation: it will be on Thursday mornings from 8:10 to 8:50. This helps children who ride the bus and cannot stay for the after-school period. It also helps avoid conflicts with after-school activities. Danielle and Marina will be working with the recent new test takers 6 days on the following Thursdays: 15th, Nov; 29th, Nov; 6th, Dec; 13th, Dec.; 20th, Dec. and 3rd, Jan. Besides the test preparation lectures on these dates, teachers are already putting test preparation into their usual courses. We are finding...\n\nQ: From the passage, we know that   _  .", "options": ["Danielle will help students prepare for different tests", "the school year test will be on a Tuesday", "all the children must take part in the test preparation", "the students can learn how to write well in the test preparation"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2098, "question": "A newspaper reporter's job can be very interesting.He meets all types of people and lives quite a busy life.He is _ for news all the time,then after several years he may get a desk job,and life becomes a bit more settled.Let's look at his work a little more closely.In a day he may have to interview the prime minister of a foreign country, and the next day he may be writing about a football match.Sometimes he may be so busy that he hardly has any time to sleep.And at other times he may go on for days looking out for news materials yet return empty--handed. In the beginning,a reporter has to cover a very wide field.After the early years he becomes more specialized in his work.For example,he may finaliy be asked to write only on court cases or politics or sports.Some reporters may become so s...\n\nQ: What's the passage mainly about?", "options": ["An introduction to a newspaper reporter's job.", "An interesting life of a newspaper reporter.", "Something written by a newspaper reporter.", "How to become a good newspaper reporter."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 828, "question": "Being connected to the Internet has become a necessary part of modern life. Some people actually need it as they cannot do their jobs without it, and others simply feel they need it as they cannot imagine life without it. To think that something that did not even exist 50 years ago has come to _ our lives like this in just about 15 years makes one wonder - just what will the future bring? In 2004, a survey was conducted in the US asking a group of technology experts their opinions on the Internet in the next ten years. 57% of them agreed that virtual classes will be more widely adopted in schools, allowing students to learn with those at the same level and with interests in the same subjects. It's quite possible that, by the year 2030, every child in every school will do all their schoolwo...\n\nQ: What is probably the best title for the passage?", "options": ["Virtual reality, our best friend!", "Goodbye, textbooks and offices!", "What will future life be like with the Internet?", "How can human beings deal with the Internet?"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2539, "question": "When you sleep somewhere else--like at summer camp or a friend's house--you know you're in for a fun time. It can be exciting to get away from the same old bed in the same old room in the same old house. But fun as this is, for some kids being away from home can be scary and sad. They want to go and have fun with their friends, but once they're there, they start to miss their good old bed, their good old parents, and all that everyday stuff at home. It's called being homesick. Homesick means you're upset, sad, and maybe scared. But don't feel surprised. A lot of people get homesick, even grownups. When you're used to having certain people and things around you, it can be scary when they're gone. When you're dealing with other problems, you will feel homesick, too. Some kids may feel more h...\n\nQ: The BEST title for this passage is \"  _  \".", "options": ["Homesickness", "Why Do You Feel Homesick", "How to Be Less Homesick", "When Will Kids Feel Homesick"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3130, "question": "WASHINGTON, Sept. 6 (Xinhua) -- U.S. President Barack Obama on Monday announced a new plan to renew and expand the nation's roads, railways and runways, in a bid to restart the _ economy and to help create jobs. Obama announced the billion-dollar infrastructure spending program at an event in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, marking the Labor Day holiday in the United States. The proposal calls for investments over six years, including rebuilding and modernizing 150,000 miles (241,350 kilometers) of roads, 4,000 miles (6,430 kilometers) of railways and 150 miles ( 241 kilometers) of runways. \"It sets up an Infrastructure Bank to leverage(;) federal dollars and focus on the smartest investment. All of this will not only create jobs now, but will make our economy run better over the long haul,\" Obama s...\n\nQ: Which of the following will be changed most in length?", "options": ["Roads.", "Railways.", "Runways.", "Highways."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1917, "question": "Jack Benny was one of the most famous names in show business.He was born in Chicago,Illinois,on February 14th,1894.His parents,Meyer and Emma Kubelsky,were religious Jews.They had moved to the United States from Eastern Europe.Benny was a quiet boy.For much of the time,his parents were busy working in his father's store.As a child,Benny learned to play the violin.After finishing his school,he joined the Navy.He continued using his violin to perform for sailors.In one show he was chosen more for his funny jokes than for his skill with the violin.That experience made him believe that his future job was a comedian. Benny developed a show personality that had all the qualities people dislike.He was known for being so _ --he refused to spend any money unless forced to do so.On his shows Benny o...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is TRUE about Benny?", "options": ["He did a good job in show business.", "His first appearance on TV was very successful.", "Most of his films became wellknown to Americans.", "He treated all his awards as nothing."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3014, "question": "We might not be alone in the universe. Actually, it may be confirmed as a very crowded place by new computer models developed to help identify habitable planets. Estimates of places where life can exist have been based on the possibility of them having surface water. But software recently developed by the Aberdeen University allows researchers to identify planets with underground water kept liquid by heat from planets. Water is fundamental for life and planets too close to the sun lose water to the atmosphere through evaporation. On the other hand, planets located in distant reaches from their star have their surface water locked away as ice. Sean McMahon, who is carrying out the work, explained: \"Traditionally people have said that if a planet is in this Goldilocks zone--not too hot and n...\n\nQ: Why did John Parnell mention the fact about Earth?", "options": ["To prove that there is majority of life on Earth.", "To prove that life may also exist in other planets.", "To prove that there is primitive life down through Earth.", "To prove that there is a habitat for microorganisms below Earth."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2904, "question": "Pulling heavy suitcases all day in the summer is hard work, especially when you are a thin 14-year-old boy. That was me in 1940-the youngest and smallest baggage boy at New York City's Pennsylvania Railway Station. After just a few days on the job, I began noticing that the other fellows were overcharging passengers. I'd like to join them, thinking, \"Everyone else is doing it.\" When I got home that night, I told my dad what I wanted to do. \"You give an honest day's work,\" he said, looking at me straight in his eye. \"They are paying you. If they want to do that, you let them do that.\" I followed my dad's advice for the rest of that summer and have lived by his words ever since. Of all the jobs I've had, it was my experience at Pennsylvania Railway Station that has stuck with me. Now I teach...\n\nQ: What can be inferred about the baggage boys?", "options": ["They could earn much, but they had to work hard.", "Many of them earned money in a dishonest way.", "They were all from poor families.", "They were thin, young boys."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 912, "question": "HOGN KONG--Nine out of 10 Singapore citizens returned dropped wallets with money in them,but in Hone Kong only three out of l0 wallets were returned in an honesty test carried out in Asian cities by Readers Digest . Larger cities did worse while in general people in smaller places returned secretly planted wallets,results from the experiment showed. Readers Digest secretly scattered 140 wallets all over Asia,each with a name,address and phone number,family pictures,notes and money in it. The magazine workers then watched to see what happened.South Koreans in Seoul returned six out of the ten dropped wallets,while those in Inchon returned eight. 50 percent of Be dropped wallets were returned in Bombay,Bangkok,Taipei and Kajang in Malaysia,with most people saying they would not keep what was...\n\nQ: It call be learned from the newspaper that Bombay is a city in  _  .", "options": ["Europe", "Asia", "the United States", "prefix = st1 /Malaysia"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3361, "question": "\"Hitler and the Germans,\" an exhibition in Berlin's German Historical Museum which aims to investigate the society that created Hitler, has seen more than 10,000 visitors walk through its doors since opening on Friday. Rudolf Trabold, a spokesman for the museum, said there were 4,000 visitors to the exhibition on the first day alone. People visiting the exhibition said they had waited as long as one and a half hours to get in. Ravi Nair, a 73-year-old Indian visitor, said: \"I had to queue for about an hour but it was worth it. The exhibition should help people in democratic countries realize that their vote is very valuable.\" Trabold said \"Hitler and the Germans\" was so popular because it was the first exhibition to explain how a man who lived on the margins of society for 30 years, in Vie...\n\nQ: \"Hitler and the Germans\" is open to   _  .", "options": ["remind people not to forget history.", "show how Hitler was hated by people", "study the society that created Hitler", "save money for economy growth"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3414, "question": "Welcome to Arundel Castle which is situated in West Sussex, England. The castle has a history of nearly 1000 years and has welcomed visitors traveling from all over the world. Arundel Castle also plays a starring role in many films. _ The White Garden is planted with soft white Iceberg Roses, and Snow White Lilies. The Rose Garden is newly planted with lovely old-fashioned English roses that are at their very best in June and July. The Organic Kitchen Garden produces a wide range of seasonal fruit and vegetables, pears, cherries and apples. _ In the Castle Shop, you will discover a wide and interesting range of gift ideas for everyone. It offers gifts and souvenirs designed to appeal to all tastes and pockets. Foods, china, books, and stationery are all available. Many are sold in this Cas...\n\nQ: Where can you park the coach?", "options": ["In Mill Road", "Inside the Castle", "In the main town car park", "At the main Castle entrance"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1875, "question": "It's fun to receive presents. It also feels good to give presents to others. So what's the best way to budget your money, shop wisely and spend smartly this holiday season? Time for kids asked for advice from Susan Beacham of Money Savvy Generation, a company that teaches money-management skills to kids. \" My first tip is to make a list and check it twice,\" says Beacham. She suggests that kids talk with their families about whom to include in their gift giving and how much to spend. Start by writing down names, Beacham says. Then put a dollar amount next to each name and add it up. Do you have enough money? If not, make changes. And don't forget---- not everyone needs a store-bought gift. Beacham points out that some of the best presents are free. Add to your list the names of people you w...\n\nQ: What's the most important thing in budgeting for presents according to Beacham?", "options": ["Spending money within the limit you have set.", "Working out how much money to spend in total.", "Deciding how much money to spend on each person.", "Checking the name list of people you will give presents"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3417, "question": "I am a professor of sports and exercise so I often deal with nervousness in my research with sports people. Actually, most people experience nervousness at some time or another. If you are feeling anxious, my advice is to first find the cause or causes. Make a list of those things that are making you nervous and work out which ones you can do something about. Focus all of your efforts on managing the causes that you can control. Most people cannot tell the difference between controllable and uncontrollable causes, so things they can't control become a big reason for nervousness. Dealing with this is very important if people want to keep a healthy mind. Simply try to accept the uncontrollable causes of nervousness. You might be worried about the weather on a big day, an accident or an attac...\n\nQ: If swimming makes you nervous, what should you do according to the writer?", "options": ["Go swimming often to get used to it.", "Avoid going to the swimming pool.", "Find a swimming teacher.", "Imagine watching others swim."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 874, "question": "I must have been about fourteen then, and I put away the incident from my mind with the easy carelessness of youth. But the words, Carl Walter spoke that day, came back to me years later, and ever since have been of great value to me. Carl Walter was my piano teacher. During one of my lessons he asked how much practicing I was doing. I said three or four hours a day. \"Do you practice , an hour at a time?\" \"I try to.\" \"Well, don't,\" he exclaimed. \"When you grow up, time won't come in long stretches. Practice in minutes, whenever you can find them five or ten before school, after lunch, between household tasks. Spread the practice through the day, and piano-playing will become a part of your life.\" When I was teaching at Columbia, I wanted to write, but class periods, theme-reading, and comm...\n\nQ: What is the best title of this passage?", "options": ["Concentrate on Your Work", "A Little at a Time", "How I Became a Writer", "Good Advice"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2847, "question": "Daniel Brown was just five years old when he climbed into the family car and let it roll away down the road. He was only three when he flooded the kitchen. His mother, Angela Brown is very busy looking after her new baby, a little girl called Laura, as well as Daniel. She told us, \"Daniel is so full of curiosity .\" At that moment, we hear a loud noise and then silence. We go upstairs and find Daniel getting out of a wardrobe which he has pulled over onto the floor, with a book in his hand. \"It's for you, Mum,\" he says and looks up at his mum and smiles. Seven-year-old Daniel has a lovely face. He has golden hair, big brown eyes, and a friendly smile. I have to admit that Daniel doesn't look like a naughty boy. Angela told me all about it, \"Once I found him as he was about to put Jasper in ...\n\nQ: What did Daniel do while his mother was talking to the author?", "options": ["He drove away the family car.", "He cut off the hair of the girl next door.", "He fell to the floor with the wardrobe.", "He flooded the kitchen."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 285, "question": "Born in America in 1898, William was an extraordinary boy, gifted with an amazing IQ between 250 and 300. The genius went to a grammar school when he was only 6 years old and graduated just within 7 months. At the age of 11, he became the youngest student of the Harvard University. He graduated with high scores at the age of 16 and entered Harvard Law School at 18. Gifted with an amazing IQ between 220 and 230, Terence Tao makes it to this list of the people with the highest IQ in the world. Born in Adelaide, Australia in 1975, this genius first displayed his incredible intelligence at a mere age of 2, when he managed to solve basic arithmetic questions on his own. At the age of 16, he graduated with both Master's and Bachelor's degrees at the Flinders University. He has been considered as...\n\nQ: How many people with remarkable IQ are mentioned in the passage?", "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2317, "question": "Where and how you eat are just as important as what you eat. Take this test to find your eating style to make sure you're getting the nutrition you need. Which statements sound like you? Group 1: # I like to make my plate look pretty before I dig in for the first bite. # I often help my parents make recipes. # I could win the first prize in the \"World's Slowest Eater\" contest. Group 2: # The crumbs in the sofa are mine -- I eat while watching TV. # I can finish a whole box of snacks quickly while I'm doing something else. # Sometimes I'm surprised to find my plate empty. Where did all the food go? Group 3: # Sometimes I eat my dinner standing up. # I spend more time in the drive-through than at the dinner table. # Breakfast? Who has time for breakfast? If you answered mostly Group 1: You e...\n\nQ: The passage is mainly about   _  .", "options": ["how to keep healthy", "whether you eat a balanced diet", "what your eating style is", "how to form a good eating habit"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2740, "question": "While Americans feel worried about how to look after their children and help them grow, French parents are raising happy, well-behaved children without all the anxiety. Pamela Druckerman, an American mother living in Paris, watched carefully as to why French children seem to behave so much better than American children. Let's listen to what she said. While eating at the restaurants in Paris, I noticed the French kids were either sitting in their chairs waiting for their food or eating fish and even vegetables, happy and satisfied. There was no shouting or crying, and there were no pieces of food around their tables. However, my 2-year-old daughter, Beth, took a brief interest in the food. She even threw food everywhere. She couldn't keep herself in her chair and ran around the table. Thoug...\n\nQ: What is this passage mainly about?", "options": ["Why French children love eating at restaurants.", "Why American children don't like eating at mealtime.", "What American parents usually learn from French parents.", "How French parents raise their children compared to American parents."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3331, "question": "Trees should only be pruned when there is a good and clear reason for doing so and , fortunately, the number of such reasons is small. First, pruning may be done to make sure that trees have a desired shape or size.The object may be to get a tree of the right height, and at the same time to help the growth of small side branches which will thicken its appearance or give it a special shape.Secondly, pruning may be done to make the tree healthier.You may cut diseased or dead wood, or branches that are rubbing against each other and thus cause wounds.The health of a tree may be encouraged by removing branches that are blocking up the centre and so preventing the free movement of air. One result of pruning is that an open wound is left on the tree and this provides an easy entry for disease, b...\n\nQ: Why is a special substance painted on the tree?", "options": ["To make a wound smooth and clean.", "To prevent disease entering a wound.", "To cover a rough surface.", "To help a wound to dry."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 380, "question": "Two thieves came to a house to steal something. They dug a hole in the wall of the house. There lived many mice in the house. The woman in the house saw a mouse crawl into the house in the moonlight. \"Look! In comes one,\" she said to the man in the house. The thief was so frightened that he hurriedly crawled out of the house and said to the one waiting outside, \"She found me when I was just in.\" But the thief outside didn't believe him, so he said, \"Let us try to crawl into the house together.\" At that time two mice happened to crawl into the house, too. The woman saw the mice and shouted, \"In come two, catch them!\" The two thieves were terribly frightened. The man in the house said, \"You saw them come in but where are they? I will catch them tonight.\" The two thieves started running away ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["The two thieves not only failed to steal things but also lost their sweet potatoes.", "Whenever they found mice, the people in the house would try to catch them.", "The two thieves ran away at once, because they thought the woman had seen them.", "The man let the woman go home for a rope, which would be used for catching the thieves."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2486, "question": "A good friend of mine was complaining about her son the other day.\"Did you notice,\" she started, \"how he didn't wait for me to get my salad before he dove into his?\" True enough, the boy attacked his plate faster than a cat in the wild.Without manners, we're no more than animals.Actually, that's not true.I've been watching and feeding a group of wild cats, and they show unusual politeness toward each other.Even when food is _ , they take turns, leaving at least a small part for the next in line. My mother educated her three children to have good manners all the time.We were made to feel very uncomfortable as if we were sitting on pins and needles until we got used to saying please, thank you, pardon me, and I'm sorry.And I have to say, while it was a painful learning experience, it was one...\n\nQ: What does the writer think of her experience of learning good manners?", "options": ["Easy and relaxing", "Painful and valuable", "Easy but useless", "Too horrible"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2418, "question": "John and Booby joined a wholesale company together just after graduation from college the same year. Both worked very hard. After several years, however, the boss promoted Bobby to the position of manager but John remained an ordinary employee . John could not take it any more, so he sent his resignation and complained that the boss did not value hard working workers but only promoted those who said good words of him. The boss knew that John worked very hard for the years. He thought for a moment and said, \"Thank you for telling me, but I have a request. I hope you will do one more thing for our company before you leave. Perhaps you will change your mind and take back your resignation.\" John agreed. The boss asked him to go and find out anyone selling watermelons in the market. John went a...\n\nQ: What can be the best title of the passage?", "options": ["More Concerned, More Successful", "How to Buy Watermelons", "Who Is More Successful", "Proud John"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2497, "question": "Have you ever wanted to feel like you were in a western film? Or maybe you wanted to feel like you were a pioneer traveling the west? It is possible to experience such things during a Wild West vacation! Here are four of the best Wild West vacation locations available: Walk the Lewis and Clark Trail Walk some or all of the 3,700 miles trail that was traversed by Mariwether Lewis and William Clark, two of the world's greatest explorers. Though not all the trails are marked, there are various stops that have been preserved by various historic societies. There is also a coach that makes a 16-day _ following the trail. This begins in St. Louis, Missouri, and ends in Astoria, Oregon. Venture Route 66 Take a tour or go to see it yourself -- ride on the famous Route 66. The road is nearly 2,500 m...\n\nQ: Which of following riding adventures can tourists take on Route 66?", "options": ["A horse riding adventure.", "A coach riding adventure.", "A motorcycle riding adventure.", "A donkey riding adventure."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3330, "question": "Trees should only be pruned when there is a good and clear reason for doing so and , fortunately, the number of such reasons is small. First, pruning may be done to make sure that trees have a desired shape or size.The object may be to get a tree of the right height, and at the same time to help the growth of small side branches which will thicken its appearance or give it a special shape.Secondly, pruning may be done to make the tree healthier.You may cut diseased or dead wood, or branches that are rubbing against each other and thus cause wounds.The health of a tree may be encouraged by removing branches that are blocking up the centre and so preventing the free movement of air. One result of pruning is that an open wound is left on the tree and this provides an easy entry for disease, b...\n\nQ: Trees become unhealthy if the gardener   _  .", "options": ["allows too many branches to grow in the middle", "does not protect them from wind", "forces them to grow too quickly", "damages some of the small side branches"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1752, "question": "As winter gives way to spring, students feel like taking outdoor activities. However, do remember that accidents can happen, such as the one that happened at Taihu Lake several weeks ago. Four students from Shanghai were killed and several were injured. There were several reasons for the accident, but if the students had worn life jackets, it would have made a big difference. Therefore, it is important to take steps to avoid accidents before going on trips whether on land or water. Here are some steps: Make sure you are physically fit for any activities. You need energy for hiking or boating after a long inactive winter. Research your route . Check the weather report so you can pack the correct things so that an unexpected downpour or high winds won't destroy your day. If you are visiting ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true?", "options": ["People usually take part in fewer activities in winter.", "Cultures play an important role in your traveling.", "People should wear comfortable shoes while traveling.", "People should never go out for activities alone."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2101, "question": "Expressions about water are almost as common as water itself. The expressionto be in hot water is a very old expression. Hot water was used five hundred years ago to mean being in trouble. One story says it got that meaning from the custom of throwing extremely hot water down on enemies attacking a castle. That no longer happens. But we still get in hot water. When we are in hot water, we are in trouble. It can be any kind of trouble--serious or not so serious. A person who breaks a law can be in hot water with the police. A young boy can be in hot water with his mother, if he walks in the house with dirty shoes. Beingin deep wateris almost the same as being in hot water. When you are in deep water, you are in a difficult position. To keep your head above wateris a colorful expression that...\n\nQ: If your argument doesn't hold water, then it is   _  .", "options": ["weak", "convincing", "logical", "disappointing"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2052, "question": "It was just three degrees above zero. \"That's cold,\" thought Jane as she got ready to deliver her morning papers. Jane has 50 customers, and on cold mornings when she couldn't ride her bike, it took her more than an hour to make her rounds. As she collected her papers and put them into a big canvas bag, Jane regretted that she hadn't finished her math homework the night before. There was still time. She'd hurry with the papers and finish the math before breakfast. Less than an hour later, Jane was nearly finished. She had only five customers to go. She could then head for home to complete her math while her mom fixed breakfast. As she rounded the corner, she saw a car in the middle of the street. It was Mr. Zimmerman, the elderly man who walked with a walking stick. His car was out of gas....\n\nQ: The best title for this reading should be   _", "options": ["Fifth Customers", "There's no Easy Answer", "No Time to Finish Homework", "A Cold Morning for Jane"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 3033, "question": "Are you a big fan of pirate stories? Do you know how to talk like a pirate? You can have fun on September 19th. This special holiday is called International Talk Like A Pirate Day. It was invented in 1995 by two young Americans, John Baur and Mark Summers. These two good friends came up with this idea when they were playing racquetball, and began to talk like pirates. At that moment, they thought, \"Young people are interested in pirate, but there is no such a chance for people to get together to share it. Why not have a day when everybody talks like a pirate?\" They decided to make September 19th the date. Since then, Baur and Summers have tried hard to promote Talk Like A Pirate Day. As Baur said, \"We've talked like pirates, and encouraged several of our friends to do so every September 19...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements is NOT true according to the passage?", "options": ["It was Dave Barry who made more people know the holiday.", "Talk Like A Pirate Day is a young, active and lively holiday", "The holiday has been popular since the birth of it.", "Thanks to John Baur and Mark Summers' imagination and creativity, many people realize the pirate dream."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 918, "question": "Joe Temper should have known better. After all, he works for a large auto insurance company. It won't hurt to leave the key in the truck this once, he thought, as he filled his gas tank at a self-service gas station. But minutes later, as he was paying the money, he saw the truck being driven away. In 2010, 1.6 million motor vehicles were stolen in the United States --one every 20 seconds. If present trends continue, experts predict vehicle thefts could be over two million every year by the end of the decade. Vehicle theft is a common phenomenon, which has a direct effect on over four million people a year. The cost is astonishing. Many police officials blame professional thieves for the large number of the thefts. It is a major moneymaker for organized crime. Typically, stolen cars are ta...\n\nQ: What type (s) of safety system can help the police find a stolen car back?", "options": ["The device that sends out radio signals.", "The device that disables the fuel pumps.", "The device that disables the starter.", "All of the above."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2004, "question": "A new report says the number of foreign students at colleges and universities in the United States increased by three percent last year. This has been the first obvious increase since 2001. American schools last fall had 583,000 foreign students. The record is 586,000. That was set in 2002 after many years of gains. But after that the numbers fell. The terrorist attacks on September 11th, 2001 led to more visa requirements. Now stronger efforts are being made to get more foreign students to study in the United States. China remained in second place in front of South Korea but behind India, whichsent almost 84,000 students last fall. The number of Japanese fell sharply by nine percent, although it remained in fourth place. There were three percent drops from Indonesia and Kenya, the only Af...\n\nQ: In which section of a newspaper could you most probably read this passage?", "options": ["Culture.", "Science.", "Education.", "Business."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 134, "question": "A 16-year-old South Dakota boy who became lost while hunting and spent 16 hours alone in the Black Hills National Forest says he was scared but still managed to make a survival plan. Austin DuVall, of Rapid City, became lost on Nov.3 while hunting with his father. He ran after a deer, and soon found himself alone. \"I ran after a deer, but I didn't get it,\" he said. \"Then I was really lost.\" He had only his hunting rifle and the clothes he was wearing. He had no food or water and had nothing that could help him find his way to safety. \"I knew that no one could hear me. I decided to just sleep and get up in the morning and find safety,\" he said. Austin climbed up on a rock and slept through the night. Then he awoke and relied on skills he learned in a hunter safety course. He followed a stre...\n\nQ: Who saved Austin according to his father?", "options": ["The couple in the cabin.", "Emergency officials.", "Volunteers.", "Himself."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2544, "question": "Music for Humans and Humpback Whales As researchers conclude in Science, the love of music is not only a universal feature of the human species, but is also deeply fixed in complex structures of the human brain, and is far more ancient than previously suspected. In the articles that discuss the field of bio-musicology, the study of the biological basis for the creation and appreciation of music, researchers present various evidence to, show that music-making is at once an original human \"business\", and an art form with skillful performers throughout the animal kingdom. The new reports stress that humans hold no copyright on sound wisdom, and that a number of nonhuman animals produce what can rightly be called music, rather than random sound. Recent in-depth analyses of the songs sung by hu...\n\nQ: The main purpose of the passage is to   _  .", "options": ["argue and discuss", "inform and explain", "compare and advertise", "examine and assess"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 810, "question": "If you like bicycling as much as you like playing ball and can't seem to decide between the two sports, you may want to consider cycle ball--a fun sport that adopts the key attributes from both activities and transforms it into a totally new game.. Also known as red ball, the game was invented in 1893 by German laborers who wished to play polo , but could not afford horses. While the sport has not _ in North America, it is very fashionable in Europe and even Japan. Played in an indoor court, cycle ball is similar to soccer in many ways--the aim is to score as many goals as possible, and only the goalkeeper is allowed to touch the ball. The one big difference? Use of legs is forbidden. Instead, players have to guide the ball across the court, using the front wheels of their bicycles or with...\n\nQ: It can be known from the passage that   _  .", "options": ["every player who is playing cycle ball is allowed to touch the ball.", "the aim of playing cycle ball is to score as many goals as possible.", "if a player touches the floor with his feet, the opposing team will win", "heads are not allowed to be used to guide the ball across the court."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 945, "question": "Recipients of this year's Annenberg scholarships were announced on June 19. Brittany Blythe was one of them. In seventh grade,Brittany Blythe dreamed of being a cheerleader . Her school's coaches were less than enthusiastic. \"They said. 'I don't know how you'll be able to do it'. \"she recalls. \"'You won't be able to do it'.\" But Brittany,now a junior at Strath Haven High School near Philadelphia,refused to give up. And when the junior school cheerleaders won a tournament last year, she was right there,dancing and cheering with the rest of the team. Not bad for someone whose legs were cut off below the knee when she was two years old. Brittany,18,was born without shinbones --\"just blood and muscle tissue,\"as she puts it. When she tried to walk, her legs twisted. After the operation, she ada...\n\nQ: What was the coaches' first attitude towards Brittany's dream?", "options": ["Supportive", "Enthusiastic", "Optimistic", "Doubtful"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 414, "question": "Grown-ups are often surprised by how well they remember something they learned as children but have never practiced ever since. A man who has not had a chance to go swimming for years can still swim as well as ever when he gets back in the water. He can get on a bicycle after many years and still ride away. He can play catch and hit a ball as well as his son. A mother who has not thought about the words for years can teach her daughter the poem that begins \"Twinkle, twinkle, little star\" or remember the story of Cinderella or Goldilocks and the Three Bears. One explanation is the law of overlearning, which can be stated as follows: Once we have learned something, additional learning trials increase the length of time we will remember it. In childhood we usually continue to practice such sk...\n\nQ: The author explains the law of overlearning by", "options": ["presenting research findings", "setting down general rules", "using examples", "making a comparison"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2262, "question": "There is an English saying that goes, \"he who laughs last, laughs the hardest.\" High School Musical star and teen heartthrob Zac Efron is laughing a lot these days. As a young boy, Efron was picked on in school because he was always the smallest in his class and teased because he had a big space between his teeth. In the sixth grade, Efron's basketball team made it to the league championships. In double overtime , with three seconds left, he rebounded the ball and passed it to the wrong team! They scored and his team lost the game. But history, as they say, is a thing of the past. Now at 21, Efron is one of People magazine's 100 Most Beautiful People, graces the cover of Entertainment Weekly, Hollywood's most influential magazine, and is traveling the world promoting the third High School ...\n\nQ: Which of the following might be the best title to the passage?", "options": ["Don't give up", "He who laughs last laughs the hardest", "Zac Efron's life story", "Zac Effort's success in musical film"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1571, "question": "Immigration is the act of coming to a foreign country to live. The act of leaving one's country to settle in another is called emigration. Immigrants who flee their country because of persecution, war, or such disasters as famines or epidemics are known as refugees or displaced persons. Most people find it very hard to pull up roots in their native land and move to a strange country. But throughout history, countless millions of people have done so. The heaviest immigration worldwide took place from the early 1800's to the Great Depression, the economic hard times of the 1930's. In that period, about 60 million people moved to a new land. Most came from Europe. More than half immigrated to the United States. Other destinations included Canada, Argentina, Brazil, Australia, New Zealand, and...\n\nQ: Most Immigrants to the United States in the nineteenth century came from   _  .", "options": ["Europe", "Asia", "Australia", "South Africa"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2985, "question": "Though the facts that too many people on earth and a too rapid increase in the number added each year are not in argument, we always begin the discussion of \"population as global issue\" with what most persons mean like this. It was quite right to compare demographic growth to \"a long, thin powder fuse that bums steadily and hesitatingly until it finally reaches the charge and explodes\". To understand the current situation, which is characterized by rapid increases in population, it is necessary to understand the history of population trends. Rapid growth is a comparatively recent phenomenon. Looking back at the 8,000 years of demographic history, we find that populations have been virtually stable or growing very slightly for most of human history. For most of our ancestors, life was hard,...\n\nQ: During the first period of demographic history, societies were often in danger of extinction because  _  .", "options": ["only one in ten persons could live past 40.", "our ancestors had little enthusiasm for more children", "there was higher mortality than fertility in most places", "it was too dangerous to have babies due to the poor conditions"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1846, "question": "Table manners are very different in every country. For example, when you are in England you must not lift your soup plate to your mouth. This is very impolite. But when you are in Japan this is completely normal. Lifting your plate to your mouth in Japan is a traditional way of drinking your soup. And also in Japan you don't have to worry about making a noise when you drink it. It just shows that you really like the food! But it is not the same in Britain, so you shouldn't make a noise when eating there. In Britain, people don't put their hands or arms on the table during the meal. But in Mexico, guests keep their hands on the table all the time. In fact, you should watch what your hands do very carefully. In Arab countries, it is impolite when you eat with your left hand, so don't do it! ...\n\nQ: It is impolite to lift the soup plate to your mouth in   _  .", "options": [".Japan", "England", ". Ukraine", ". Mexico"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 553, "question": "Mo Yan, whose primitive name is Guan Moye, was awarded the Nobel Literature Prize on October 11, 2012.\"Chinese author Mo Yan today won the Nobel Literature Prize for writing that mixes folk tales, history and the contemporary,\" the Swedish Academy announced.\"Through a mixture of fantasy and reality, historical and social perspectives, Mo Yan has created a world reminiscent in its complexity of those in the writing of William Faulkner and Gabriel Garcia Marques, at the same time finding a departure point in old Chinese literature and in oral tradition,\" the Swedish Academy said Mo Yan began writing in 1981 and he has published novels, short stories and essays on various topic, and despite his social criticism is seen in his homeland as one of the foremost contemporary authors, the Nobel Com...\n\nQ: Why was Mo Yan awarded the Nobel Literature Prize of 2012?", "options": ["Because of his work The Frog.", "Because of his works with the contemporary.", "Because of his works with history.", "Because his writing mixes folk tales, history and the contemporary."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 587, "question": "Some mothers in Senegal are learning a new way to save the lives of babies born too soon. The idea is borrowed from the way mother kangaroos carry their young in front in a pouch. The baby kangaroo stays in this built-in baby carrier until it can survive independently. Kangaroo mother care is also known as the skin-to-skin method for premature babies. The direct contact with the mother keeps the baby warm. It also lets the baby breastfeed at any time. The mother's heartbeat also helps control the baby's breathing rate. Every year, seven thousand babies are born at the health center where Ousmane Ndiaye works in Guediaway, outside Dakar. One in five is underweight. But Senegal has few incubators in which to keep premature babies warm. In Africa, one newborn in twenty dies. A major reason is...\n\nQ: What is the passage mainly about ?", "options": ["advantages of kangaroo mother care", "new ways to take care of newborn babies", "medical conditions in Senegal need improving", "saving premature babies with an idea from nature"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2963, "question": "Advertisers tend to think big and perhaps this is why they're always getting criticism. Their critics seem to resent(...) them because they have a gift for self-promotion and because they have so much money to throw around. 'It's unjust,' they say, 'that this entirely unproductive industry (if we can call it that) should absorb millions of pounds each year. It only goes to show how much profit the big companies are making. Why don't they stop advertising and reduce the price of their goods? After all, it's the consumer who pays...' The poor old consumer! He'd have to pay a great deal more if advertising didn't create mass markets for products. It is precisely because of the heavy advertising that consumer goods are so cheap. But we get the wrong idea if we think the only purpose of adverti...\n\nQ: The attitude of the author toward advertisers is  _", "options": ["appreciative.", "trustworthy.", "critical", "dissatisfactory."], "answer": 0}]